[
    {
        "cell_ids": [
            1,
            2
        ],
        "question": "What are the two matrices resulting from matrix factorization?",
        "answer": "U is a representation of users in some low dimensional space, and V is a representation of items.",
       "task": "Recommendation Systems",
        "skill": "Matrix Factorization"
    },
  {
        "cell_ids": [
           2
        ],
       "question": "What is the goal of matrix factorization in recommendation systems?",
       "answer": "to populate the utility matrix by finding similarities between users and items.",
        "task": "Recommendation Systems",
        "skill":"Matrix Factorization"
    },
      {
        "cell_ids": [
            2
        ],
        "question": "What does the cost function in matrix factorization aim to minimize?",
        "answer": "Mean squared error over the utility matrix.",
        "task": "Recommendation Systems",
        "skill": "Matrix Factorization"
   },
    {
        "cell_ids": [
           5
        ],
        "question": "What is the shape of the dataframe after merging movie and rating data?",
        "answer": "(20000797, 6)",
        "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
         "skill":"Basic Data Analysis"
    },
     {
        "cell_ids": [
             5
         ],
        "question": "What are the column names of the combined dataframe?",
         "answer":"movieId, title, genres, userId, rating, timestamp",
        "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
         "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
    },
   {
        "cell_ids": [
            9
        ],
         "question": "What is the embedding size used in the matrix factorization model?",
        "answer": "8",
        "task": "Recommendation Systems",
         "skill":"Matrix Factorization"
    },
    {
        "cell_ids": [
            10
         ],
         "question": "What is the loss function used during training?",
         "answer":"MSE",
        "task": "Recommendation Systems",
        "skill": "Matrix Factorization"
    },
  {
        "cell_ids": [
            10
         ],
       "question": "What is the evaluation metric used during training?",
       "answer": "MAE",
       "task":"Recommendation Systems",
       "skill": "Matrix Factorization"
    },
    {
        "cell_ids": [
            13
         ],
         "question": "What is the RMSE score of the best model from the GridSearchCV?",
        "answer":"0.930229238035991",
         "task": "Recommendation Systems",
        "skill": "Matrix Factorization"
    },
    {
         "cell_ids": [
            15
        ],
       "question": "What are the best parameters obtained from the grid search for SVD model",
      "answer": "{'n_epochs': 5, 'lr_all': 0.005}",
      "task": "Recommendation Systems",
       "skill":"Matrix Factorization"
    }
]